当用户的location preference 被存储后
Once the user's location preference has been stored. When do
我们什么时候该使用它呢？我们需要首选地理位置用来
we make use of it? We need the preferred location on
查询气象服务。幸运的是，在第二节中，我们
we query the weather service. Luckily, in lesson 2, we
修改了天气去接受地理位置参数。
modified fetch weather task to accept a location parameter. We hard
我们将它硬解码为山景城的邮编
coded it to be the Mountain View zip code. But
但是现在我们需要使用存储在SharePreference中的地理位置
now we should use the location stored in shared preferences. We
我们并没有明确地向你展示如何实现，所以你可能需要
haven't explicitly shown you how to do this. So you might
查阅资料，可以在Android developer的网址上
need to do some digging around. On the Ander developer site
弄清楚如何实现它。当你
to figure out how to do it. Once
完成了这个任务后，勾选这个方框并继续
you've made the change, check the box to continue.